iloho.com 2009-07-14

# iloho.com | Privacy Policy

* iloho takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting the iloho website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers iloho’s treatment of personal information that it gathers when you are on the iloho website and when you use iloho services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that iloho does not own or control, or to individuals that iloho does not employ or manage.

* * *

What this Privacy Policy Covers

* This Privacy Policy covers iloho’s treatment of personally identifiable information that iloho collects and receives when you are on the iloho website, and when you use iloho's services.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that iloho does not own or control, or to people that iloho does not employ or manage.

* * *

Information Collection and Use

* **General**

iloho collects personally identifying information when you register for an iloho account, when you use certain iloho products or services, when you sign-up for the iloho newsletter and when you enter promotions or competitions.

iloho uses this information for the following general purposes: to improve your online experience, to improve our services, to contact you, to conduct research, to administer the website and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

When you register with iloho, we ask for your name, email address, date of birth, gender and location. Once you register with iloho and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

  1. Registration: In order for you to use Iloho services, such as submitting new links to the website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your email address.

Email: From time to time, iloho may send you email notifications regarding news from iloho or changes in service. iloho will never ask for your password nor ask you to divulge personal information via email. Users will be given the option to opt out of email communication. If you do not receive this option, you may always opt out by contacting newsletter@iloho.com.

iloho automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, iloho cookie information, and the page you requested.

  1. iloho may also display the total counts that any page has been viewed. This includes member profile pages.

Social sharing of data: Iloho allows other users to browse stories that you have rated, submitted, blogged or commented on. This information is made available via your member profile (iloho.com/users/username) or within the permalink URL of the story in which you performed the action on. iloho may choose to post this data on other site features in the future and within its newsletters.

Profile information: iloho allows other users to browse your full name, location, and instant messaging URL, within your member profile should you provide this optional information.

Syndication: Iloho allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.

Friends Data: Much like other social services Iloho allows non-friends to browse through your friends activities (iloho.com/users/usersname/friends).

API: Iloho will allow third parties access to all iloho data this is already publicly available through www.iloho.com. iloho will forever keep private passwords and blog settings.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While iloho will not be able to provide you with a personalised experience if we cannot recognise you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

* iloho will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone.

iloho will only share your personal information as described below:

  1. **iloho personnel:**

iloho personnel (including consultants, contractors and agencies) may have access to user information while carrying out their duties in the normal course of iloho business.

**Business transfers:**

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if iloho, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

**Protection of iloho and others:**

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of iloho, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**With your consent:**

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information by opting out.

* * *

Keeping your information safe

* Your iloho account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

* * *

Cookies

* iloho may set and access cookies on your computer.

iloho cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of iloho's most attractive features. 

Some of iloho’s business partners – e.g. advertisers – may set and access cookies on your computer. Other companies’ user of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. We have no access or control over third party cookies.

* * *

Your Account Information and Preferences

* iloho gives you the ability access and edit your personal information on the website at any time. Once you have logged into your account visit your profile setting page located at http://iloho.com/users/<usersname>/profile

You may request deletion of your iloho account by emailing support@iloho.com and confirming your choice to terminate the account.

iloho may send out e-mails with news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from iloho, which inform you of actions (e.g. friend requests, group activity) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please email support@iloho.com. Please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices from us.

* * *

Posting on publicly accessible areas

* A publicly accessible area is any area of iloho that is accessible by the general public and may be indexed by search engines.

You should exercise caution if you choose to disclose personally identifiable information in a publicly accessible area. Remember that this information may remain indefinitely in the publicly accessible area of iloho.

You are solely responsible for any personally identifiable information that you disclose and disseminate on publicly accessible areas.

If you have a concern about any personally identifiable information you have posted on any publicly accessible areas and are unable to delete or edit it, please refer your query to support@iloho.com.

* * *

Users under 18 years of age

* You must be 13 years or above to register to use the iloho website. As a result, iloho does not specifically collect information about children.

If we learn that iloho has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you are under the age of 18 we recommend that you receive your parents' permission before using iloho or sending information about yourself, or anyone else, over the Internet.

* * *

Changes to this Privacy Policy

* iloho may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the iloho website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed.

* * *

Questions or Suggestions

* If you have questions or suggestions please email support@iloho.com.

* * *
